Indiana History mss., 1725-1973 LMC 1544 LMC 1544
Lilly Library
Indiana History mss.
1725-1973
Lilly Library
Adams, John Quincy, 1767-1848.
Bray, William G. (William Gilmer), 1903-1979.
Harrison, Benjamin, 1833-1901
Jackson, Andrew, 1767-1845.
Jennings, Jonathan, 1784-1834
Kellogg, Miner K. (Miner Kilbourne), 1814-1889.
Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865.
Monroe, James, 1758-1831.
Morton, Oliver P. (Oliver Perry), 1823-1877
Owen, Robert, 1771-1858
Owen, Robert Dale, 1801-1877
Polk, James K. (James Knox), 1795-1849.
Ray, James Brown, 1794-1848.
Stephenson, David Curtis, 1891-1966.
Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862
Vigo, Francis, 1747-1836.
Wylie, Theophilus Adam, 1810-1895
Lilly, Josiah Kirby, 1893-1966, former owner.
LMC 1544
108.9 Linear Feet 14 boxes, 57 volumes, 40 oversize
The Indiana History mss., 1725-1973, consists of individual items related to the history of the state of Indiana, acquired separately either as a gift, purchase, transfer, or removal from a variety of sources.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Acquisition Information
Received from numerous sources at various times. Accession information is given for the majority of entries. The most recent addition was made in 1997.
Historical Note
Indiana is a state that is part of the American Midwest. Sitting at the "crossroads of America," Indiana borders Lake Michigan to the north, Illinois to the west, Ohio to the east, and Kentucky to the south. Indiana was the 19th state to enter the union, being admitted on December 11, 1816. Indianapolis became the state capital in 1825. The state is known for its people, known as "Hoosiers,"; its industries, including agriculture, quarrying, and mining; and its transportation infrastructure.
The area that would later become the state of Indiana was first inhabited by members of the Miami Confederation, including the Miami and Potawatomi. In the late 17th and early 18th centuries, French traders established the first white settlements in the area. After the land was claimed for the United States during the American Revolution, it was added to the Northwest Territory by the Ordinance of 1787. The 18th century brought with it an influx of white immigrants and settlers to the area, leading to a series of conflicts with the native inhabitants. Battles continued until 1811, when the Battle of Tippecanoe was won by future-president William Henry Harrison. Further settlement of the area and statehood soon followed.
Scope and Content Note
This collection covers the history of Indiana from 1725-1973. It consists of correspondence, diaries, minutes, financial records, memoirs, articles about specific areas of the state, and legal documents.
Note on Indexing Term - "North America--History--Colonial period, ca. 1600-1775": Of particular interest is an alphabetical biographical list, "Revolutionary soldiers buried in Indiana", Dec. 12, 1915.
Note on Indexing Term - "Education": Of interest is a two volume diary dated 1855-1857 written by David Eckley Hunter, a teacher in Elletsville, Indiana. Also of interest are forty-two notes, papers and letters dated Dec. 6, 1921-May 21, 1922 to Doyne Trout Koonce in answer to a request from her for information relating to the normal school movement in Indiana for use in her master's thesis.
Note on Indexing Term - "Labor unions and socialism": Of interest: "Report on the Subject of Employment" by Josiah Kirby Lilly dated 1916. This bears a quotation by J.K. Lilly Sr., and J.K. Lilly, Jr. on the value of employees to a company.
Note on Indexing Term - "Law": Of particular interest: July 7, 1790: Warrant for the arrest of John Ellis. June 29, 1816: photostat of the Constitution of the state of Indiana. Jan. 11-Aug. 2, 1819: Papers relating to William Hunt's trial in Wayne County, Indiana. 1853-1856: Documents related to the legal career of Oliver Perry Morton in Wayne County, Indiana. Apr. 11-Aug. 29, 1864: Diary of Jabez Thomas Cox, lawyer and judge. May 1868: Complaint-Lambdin P. Milligan vs. James R. Slack and others in the Court of Common Pleas, Huntington County, Indiana. 1876-1885: Docket No. One for Westchester Township, Porter County, Indiana written by John Gondring, justice of the peace. 1912-1915: Reading notes concerning wills and legal provisions written by Benjamin Blumber, lawyer of Terre Haute, Indiana. undated: manuscripts decisions written by David Demaree Banta, dean of Indiana University Law School. undated: "Youthful Studies: Law Notes" written by lawyer Stephen C. Stevens.
Note on Indexing Term - "Medicine": Of particular interest are: 1860, Sept. 12-1897, May 27. Ledger listing charges for medical services of Edwin W. Magann, physician. 1861, Apr. 6-1896, Feb. 23. Daybook listing charges for medical service of Edwin W. Magann, physician. 1864, Mar. 18-1865, July 16. Letter-book of circulars, general orders and special orders to the medical section of the 9th Indiana cavalry. 1865, Apr. 17. Letter from Will H. Morgan to his mother. Morgan comments on his success as a medicine salesman.
Note on Indexing Term - "Religion": Some of those of a religious nature are described as follows: 1835, Sept. 30-1841, Aug. 14. Account book of Indiana Yearly Meeting of Friends. 1844, Sept.25-1851, Oct. 15 (copy). Minutes of the Indiana conference of the Methodist Episcopal Church. 1917, Feb. 26. John Poucher, clergyman. A religious survey of Orleans, Indiana. n.d. J.B. Cunningham, Early churches and church work in Indiana.
For digitized content, see Digital Collections.
Arrangement Note
Arranged chronologically. Undated items are arranged alphabetically at the end of the series.
Banks and banking --Indiana.; French --Indiana.; Hoosier (Nickname).; Tippecanoe, Battle of, Ind., 1811.; Indians of North America --Indiana.; Arithmetic --Problems, exercizes, etc.; Prices --Indiana.; Agriculture --Indiana.; Education --Indiana.; Business enterprises --Indiana.; North America--History--Colonial period, ca. 1600-1775; Education; Labor unions and socialism; Law; Medicine; Religion; United States--History--Civil War, 1861-1865; Northwest, Old --History.; Indiana --History --To 1787.; Indiana --History --Civil War, 1861-1865.; Indiana --History.; Indiana --Description and travel.; Indiana --Church history.; Indiana --Commerce.; Vincennes University --History.; Ku Klux Klan (1915- )--Indiana.; Bryan, William Lowe, 1860-1955; Dresser, Paul, 1858-1906; Lilly, Josiah Kirby, 1893-1966, former owner.
- Indiana History
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically at the item level, undated items are further arranged alphabetically.
  - [Documents relating to the French period in Indiana preserved in the Chicago Historical Society]., 1725, Mar. 31-1763, Jan. 25 -; 8 Autograph Document Signed, 9 items, 12 p. 12-36 cm.; genreform: photostats. (Box 1)
    Scope and Content
    Contents:
    [1] Reçu de Pierre Bourdon en faveur de François stats Bibeau et Antoine Robert: signé aussi par Claude Robillard, mars 31, 1725. 1 p.
    [2] Association, à Détroit, entre D'Ainault, commandant au fort St. Philippe des miamis et Pierre Roy, devaut M. de Boishébert, juin 3, 1732. 4 p.
    [3] Procuration de Chs-Frs de Mézière en faveur de son épouse Suzanne Nolan, Signée aux Ouantanons, mars 26, 1734. 1 p.
    [4] Engagment de Joseph Jérôme, de Laprairie, à Chs-François de La Pérade, commandant au poste des Miamis, pour conduire un canot de merchandises de Montréal à Détroit, mai 23, 1738. 1 p.
    [5] Transport, à Montréal, du permis de traite de Louis Godefroy de … [Normanville], commandant aux Ouantanons, à François Augé et Pierre Bissonnet, marchands de Montréal, juin 4, 1738. 1 p.
    [6] Reçu d'Etienne Dumont, commandant aux Miamis, en faveur de M. Levine, Montréal, mai 26, 1749. 1 p.
    [7] Billet de concession par St. Ange à Baptiste Racine, au poste de Vincennes, janv. 25, 1763. 1 p.
    Titles in contents taken from Honorius Provost's "inventiare des documents concernant l'historie du Canada conserves aux archives de Chicago – II – Société historique de Chicago." Revue d'historie de l'Amérique française, IV; 591-600, March 1951. English translation of no. [5] printed in Frances Krauskopf, trans. And ed. "Quiatanon Documents" in Indiana Historical Society Publications, XVIII, No. 2, Indianapolis, 1955, pp.184-185.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Gift. 9 items.
  - St. Ange de Bellerive, Louis, 1701-1774, soldier. Farewell proclamation May 18 at Vincennes, Indiana., 1764, May 18 -; Photostat of Autograph Document Signed 1 p. 34 cm. (Box 1)
    In French with interlinear English translation. Printed in Jacob Piatt Dunn's "Documents Relating to the French Settlements of the Wabash," Indiana Historical Society Publications, II, No. 11, Indianapolis, 1894, pp. 407-408.
    Custodial History
    Original in the possession of Mrs. Theodore Vonnegut, Indianapolis, Indiana. 1933.
  - Gamelin, Pierre, fl. 1790. Warrant for the arrest of John Ellis of Knox County, Indiana, the case to be tried Jan. 5, 1791, at Post Vincennes, on a plea of trespass against Robert Johnston. Issued by Pierre Gamelin, esquire., 1790, July 7 -; Autograph Document 1 p. 15 cm. (Box 1)
    Typescript included.
    Gift. 1946-1947
  - Sargent, Winthrop, 1753-1820, secretary of the Northwest Territory. Cincinnati, Ohio. Commission appointing Paul Gamelin of Vincennes, Ind. to be treasurer of Knox County, Ind., 1792, Sept. 3 -; Document Signed 1 p. 32 cm. (Box 1)
  - Inventory of goods left at Anderson's Creek., 1794, Sept. 3 -; 4 p. 32.5 cm. (Box 1)
    Source and date unknown.
  - Baird, Samuel, fl. 1795, Knox County, Indiana. To Nelson County, Kentucky to take the deposition of William Briggs, witness in a suit of trespass and ejectment, pending in the Knox County Court of Commons Pleas, between Henry Pea, plaintiff and Anne Sturgerts, defendant., 1795, May 5 -; Document Signed 1 p.; 20 x 32 cm. (Box 1)
  - Vigo, Francis, 1747-1836, soldier, merchant. Bond as administrator of the Aug. 28 estate of Amable Garguipee., 1801, Aug. 28 -; Document Signed 2 p. 30 cm.; folio.; genreform: photostat. (Box 5)
    Signed by John Rice Jones as surety and by Samuel McKee and Marston G. Clark as witnesses.
    Photostat of original donated to Indiana State Library by Guy M. Walker, 1917.
    Accompanied by a typewritten discussion of the above bond by Guy M. Walker. 3 p. 28 cm.
    Gift. 1952
  - Trial documents relating to the hiring of a slave woman in Jeffersonville, Clark County, Indiana Territory., 1806 -; Manuscript, 3 p. (Box 1)
    Collection consists of mss. trial documents related to the hiring of an African American slave woman, referred to as "Milly." The lawsuit was issued by the plaintiffs, Abraham Hite and Robert Breckenridge, for payment for the temporary hiring of "Milly" from them by the defendants, John H. Shults and John Hord. The first item is the plaintiffs' official statement with the details of the case, including the terms of the contract that was breached, undated, written either in November or December of 1806. The second item is a summons order to apperhend the defendants, dated 31 December 1806, signed by Samuel Gwathmey, head of the Land Register Office, and includes a red wax seal. The signature of the Sheriff of Clark County, Willis W. Goodwin, is on the verso. Verso annotations states that John Hord was not found, but John H. Shults was detained and appeared before Marston G. Clark. The third item is a bail agreement for John H. Shults.
    Purchase. 2012
  - Vincennes University, Vincennes, Indiana, Minutes and proceedings, Dec. 6, 1806-Apr. 24, 1824; Nov. 4, 1828-Aug. 23, 1836; June 11, 1838-June 1, 1885., 1806, Dec. 6-1885, June 1 -; Autograph & Typed Document, 6 items, 4 v. 28-29 cm. (Bound 1)
    1806 – Apr., 1867 are negative Photostats from the originals in the possession of Vincennes University; May, 1867 – June, 1885 are typescripts from the originals in the same place.
    v. 1, Dec. 6, 1806-Aug. 2, 1811
    v. 2, Apr. 13, 1811-Apr. 24, 1824; Oct. 3, 1828-Aug. 23, 1836
    v. 3, June 11, 1838-Apr. 1, 1867
    v. 4, May 6, 1867-June 15, 1885.
    Parts published:
    - Dec. 6, 1806-Sept. 12, 1807
    - Oct. 16, 1807-Dec. 11, 1811
    - Apr. 6, 1812-Apr. 24, 1824
    - Oct. 3, 1828-July 4, 1842
    - Feb. 5, 1843-July 3, 1849,
    ed. by Robert Constantine.
    Indiana Magazine of History:
    L1V: 313-364, Dec., 1958
    LV: 247-293, Sept., 1959
    LV11: 311-367, Dec. 1961
    L1X: 323-387, Dec. 1963
    LX: 159-198, June 1964.
    Purchased. 1930-1931
  - Vigo, Francis, 1747-1836, soldier, merchant. Vincennes, Ind. To the editor, of the ______. Refers to Aaron Burr's conspiracy and the treachery of George Morgan., 1807, Oct. 18 -; Typed Document 2 p. 33 cm.; copy. (Box 1)
    Appears to be incomplete. Lacks signature, and "subjoined letters and certificates" mentioned in last sentence.
  - Trueblood, Josiah, 1796-1878?, farmer. Arithmetic sum-book., 1808, Jan. 18-1819 -; Autograph Document Signed [141] p. 31 cm. (Box 1)
    According to typed "Background of the book" laid in this arithmetic sum-book Josiah Trueblood emigrated to Orange County, Indiana, from North Carolina some time around 1812.
    Gift. 1953
  - Indiana Territory Ohio River Ferry Bond. Harrison County: Bond to guarantee the establishment and upkeep of a ferry across the Ohio River., 9 Sept. 1810 (Box 1)
  - Badollet, John, 1758-1837, land commissioner. Vincennes, Indiana. To Jonathan Jennings, Delegate for the Indiana Territory in Congress. Reports on the Indian situation before and during the Battle of Tippecanoe: "Notwithstanding the repeated entreaties of the Prophet and his band for peace, Our Western Alexander pushed on to their town …. Till then the Indians had not committed one act of hostility…", 1811, Dec. 4 -; Autograph Letter Signed [2] p. 25 cm. (Box 1)
    Written above body of letter, in same hand: "Copy of a Letter addressed to Jonathan Jennings Esq. Delegate…"
    Purchase. 1994
  - Indiana Territory Harrison County $800 performance bond, 20 Feb. 1812 (Box 1)
  - Indiana Territory Harrison County $110 performance bond, 18 Aug. 1812 (Box 1)
  - Prices current at Vincennes, Indiana territory from Sept. 1812 to Mar. 1813., 1812, Sept.-1813, Mar. -; Document 2 p. 33 cm. (Box 1)
    Prices of alcoholic beverages, food and drugs. Statement that prices as given are correct, sign by Charles Smith, Will Jones and Toussaint Dubois, Jr. in the presence of George R. C. Sullivan. Statement of the increase of prices of medicine in Lexington, Ky. "owing to the great quantity purchased by the United States agents, for the N.W. army under Genl. Harrison, "signed by George R.C. Sullivan. Character testimonial for the merchants, Charles, Smith, Will Jones & Toussaint Dubois, jr., signed by Benjamin Parke, Jan. 26, 1815.
  - Franklin County voucher for payment of expenses of caring for a pauper, signed by Enoch McCarty (1783-1857), 17 May 1813 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Signed by Enoch McCarty (1783-1857) clerk of the court of common pleas. McCarty was delegate to Indiana state constitutional convention, 1816; Indiana state senate, 1832-34; state house of representatives, 1835-37; Presidential Elector for Indiana, 1836.
  - Indiana Territory Harrison County: William Logan killed a hog with a club, 19 Oct. 1812 (Box 1)
  - Indiana Territory Franklin County: Samuel Garrison's claim for the bounty of one wolf scalp, signed by Nicholas Reagan, justice of peace, 15 Sept. 1813 (Box 1)
  - Indiana Territory Franklin County deed, section no. 10, 90 acres, signed by Enoch McCarty, recorder and Samel Rockafellar, 9 Nov. 1813 (Box 1)
  - Indiana Territory Harrison County, $200 performance bond, 2 Apr. 1814 (Box 1)
  - Lane, Daniel, and Dunning, Mark, of Knox County, Indiana territory. Liquor license bond by which they are "bound into Thomas Posey Esquire Governor of … Indiana Territory.", 1813, June 26 -; Document Signed 1 p. 24 cm. (Box 1)
    Gift. Transferred from Indiana University Main Library, Bloominton, Indiana. 1941
  - Noble, James (1785-1831) senator from Indiana 1816-1831, signature as witness on a promissory note, 20 Sept. 1814 (Box 1)
  - Gamelin, Francois, Detroit, Michigan To Monsieur Dericherville, his nephew and guardian of the children of his brother, Paul Gamelin, Vincennes, Ind. Deals with the estate of Francois Gamelin's father and his poverty., 1814, Oct. 9 -; Letter Signed 3 p. 32 cm. (Box 1)
  - Indiana Territory Harrison County: petition and bond for the establishment of a ferry across the Ohio River, 1814 (Box 1)
  - Indiana Territory Harrison County, promissory note, Corydon, 1814 (Box 1)
  - Indiana Territory Harrison County, $200 performance bond, 25 Feb. 1815 (Box 1)
  - Knox County, Ind. Bill of Elihu Stout to Knox County, Ind. for $5.50 for advertising., 1815, Mar. 4 -; Autograph Document Signed 1 p. 11 cm. (Box 1)
  - Knox County, Ind. Court of Claims. Instructing the treasurer of Knox County to pay to Samuel Lane the sum of $32.89., 1815, Mar. 15 -; Document Signed 1 p. 11 cm. (Box 1)
    Printed form numbered 1.
    Signed by D. Sullivan, R. Buntin, and J. W. McCall.
  - Indiana Territory Franklin County autograph surety bond signed by Jonathan McCarty, deputy sheriff, 12 Jun. 1815 (Box 1)
  - Indiana History, Harrison County, Corydon: bond for court costs, 23 Jun. 1815 (Box 1)
  - Indiana (Territory). Census, 1815, Autograph Document Signed 1 p. 40 cm.; folio.; genreform: facsimile. (Box 5)
    The numbers of inhabitants of the Indiana Territory taken in the year 1815 by an act of the Legislature for the purpose.
    Gift. 1951
  - Latrobe, Benjamin Henry, 1764-1820, architect, engineer. Washington, D.C. To Jonathan Jennings, House of Representatives U.S., Washington, D.C. Concerns an opinion of sketch of a machine for raising water., 1816, Mar. 3 -; Autograph Letter Signed 3 p. 22-28 cm.; genreform: photostat. (Box 1)
    Photostate from original in the possession of Mrs. Minnie Graham Zapp, New Albany, Ind.
  - Horwitz, Jonathan, physician. Madison, Indiana. Territory. To Mr. Flugel, merchant, Vevay, Indiana Territory. Refers to Mrs. Flugel's illness., 1816, May 13 -; Autograph Letter Signed 3 p. 25 cm. (Box 1)
    From the library of Josiah Kirby Lilly, Jr., Indianapolis, Indiana. 1956
  - Noble, James (1785-1831), autograph note signed as defendant's attorney. Franklin County, 20 May 1816 (Box 1)
    James Noble (1785-1831) senator from Indiana, 1816-1831, Republican; Crawford Republican; Adams; Anti-Jackson; member of the convention to draft the Indiana constitution in 1816.
  - Indiana. Constitution., 1816, June 29 -; Autograph Document Signed 67[i.e. 69] p. 21-42 cm.; genreform: photostat. (Box 1)
    The constitution of the state of Indiana and the ordinance adopted by the convention accepting the propositions of the Congress of the U.S. of April 19, 1816, entitled "An act to enable the people of the Indiana Territory to form a State Government…"
    Negative Photostat from the original in the Indiana Historical Society Library.
  - Indiana Territory Jackson County, lawsuit concerning horse swapping, July 1816-8 Jul. 1817 (Box 1)
  - Jennings, Johathan, 1784-1843, governor of Ind. To John Kennedy Grahma. Introducing Capt. John Carr., 1816, July 26 -; Letter Signed 1 p. 26 cm.; genreform: photostat. (Box 1)
    Photostat from original in the possession of Mrs. Minnie Graham Zapp, New Albany, Ind. Printed in Indiana Magazine of History, XXXIX: 291, Sept. 1943.
  - Franklin County promissory note payable in 100 gallons of whisky, signed by John Amote, Daniel Tegarden, William Uammatic, and William H. Eads., 10 Aug. 1816 (Box 1)
    William H. Eads was delegate to Indiana state constitutional convention, 1816.
  - Davis, Amos and Ruth to Gallion, John, letter on the sale of land in Indiana, 1816 Aug. 13 (Box 1)
    Gift of Faith Hippensteel, 9/28/98-99
  - Franklin County, indictment for selling whisky without a license, Oct 1816 (Box 1)
  - Franklin County, indictment for assault and battery, Oct. 1816 (Box 1)
  - Franklin County, summons for Amos Butler and William McCoy signed by John Test, clerk of courts, and Jonathan McCarty, sheriff, 13 Feb. 1817 (Box 1)
    Folder includes some biographical background on Jonathan McCarty (1795-1852)
  - Franklin County, Brookville, Indiana summons for James Agins signed by Johnathan McCarty, sheriff, 13 February 1817 (Box 1)
  - Franklin County summons signed by Enoch McCarty, 25 Feb. 1817 (Box 1)
  - Franklin County, summons issued by Enoch McCarty, clerk of court and Robert Hanna, sheriff, 11 Sept. 1817 (Box 1)
  - Franklin County, Brookville, Indiana, summons signed by Enoch McCarty, clerk of courts, 30 Apr. 1817 (Box 1)
  - Noble, James, autograph note signed as defendant's attorney, 1817 (Box 1)
    James Noble (1785-1831) senator from Indiana, 1816-1831, Republican; Crawford Republican; Adams;Anti-Jackson; member of the convention to draft the Indiana constitution in 1816.
  - Minutes of the Salem, Indiana, Peace Society., 1818, Dec. 19-1827, May 12 -; Autograph Document 38 leaves. 28-32 cm.; xerox copy. (Box 1)
    Printed in Indiana Magazine of History. LXIV, no. 4 (December, 1968), 299-322.
    Original in the possession of the Hobbs Family, Plainfield, Indiana.
    Gift. 1969
  - Taylor, Waller, 1774?-1826, U.S. Senator. Washington D.C. To Jedidiah Morse. Corrections in Morse's account of the "Territory and now State of Indiana:" counties, towns, Indians, rivers, prairies., 1819, Jan. 1 -; Autograph Letter Signed 6 p. 25 cm. (Box 1)
    Purchase. 1957
  - Brown, Basil, -1849, tavern owner. Ledger of tavern at Princeton, Ind., 1819, Jan. 1-1822, May 12 -; Autograph Document Signed 361 p. 31 cm. (Bound 2)
    Accounts for prominent persons include
    Morris Birkbeck,
    Toussaint Du Bois,
    Robert Morgan Evans,
    George Flower,
    Elias Pym Fordham,
    Samuel Hall,
    David Hart,
    John Ingle,
    General Washington Johnston,
    James Kirkman,
    John Law,
    Donald Macdonald,
    James McClure,
    William Prince,
    Frederick Rapp,
    David Robb.
    Gift. 1960
  - Methodist Episcopal church. Conferences. Ohio. Papers relating to William Hunt's trial in Wayne County, Aug. 2 Indiana., 1819, Jan. 11-1819, Aug. 2 -; Letter & Document Signed, 5 items, 10 p. 17-31 cm (Box 1)
    Documents signed by
    Moses Crume,
    William Hunt,
    John Strange,
    William P. Finley,
    Allen Wiley,
    Thomas Marshill,
    Rebeccah Thornberry,
    Joseph Thornburg.
  - Jennings, Jonathan, 1784-1834, governor of Indiana. Corydon. Commission to Stephen Beers a Justice of the Peace for Floyd County., 1819, Mar. 16 -; Document Signed 4 p.; 19 x 31 cm. (Box 1)
  - Indiana. State bank. [Reports and papers.], 1819, Apr. 29-1824, Jan. 9 -; Document 48 p. 28 cm. (Box 1)
    Typewritten copy.
    Gift. Transferred from Indiana University Main Library, Bloomington, Indiana. 1919
  - [Documents related to the history of Warrick County, Indiana.], 1819-1857 -; Autograph Documents Signed, 6 items, 10 leaves. 12-33 cm. (Box 1)
    1) 1819, Oct. 21 – Joseph Arnold solemnized the bands of matrimony between Reuben Bates and Almire Day
    2) 1829, Oct. 17 – authorization by John A. Graham for the marriage of Ephraim Brooner and Mary Greenaway, solemnized by Jesse Spradley
    3) 1830, Apr. 21 – authorization by John A. Graham for Jesse Spradley to join in matrimony Hiram Brooner and Milly Taylor
    4) 1831, May 7 – authorization by John A. Graham for the marriage of Peter Brooner and Nancy A. Hardy, solemnized by Jesse Spradley
    5) 1834, Apr. 22-Nov. 7 – account of Samuel Bogan with A.M. Phelps for "sugar, thread, calico, shoes…"
    6) 1857, Aug. 4 – certified list by D. F. Bates for trustees of F & AAY Masons, Lodge No. 174 of Newburgh, Ind. Formerly in the library of King V. Hostick of Springfield, Illinois.
    Purchase. 1985